neusoft.com 2012-12-14

# Neusoft - Privacy Statement

**Statement:** Neusoft Corporation (Neusoft) is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement explains data collection and use practices of Neusoft.com (hereinafter called the Site). By accessing the Site, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this Privacy Statement.

**1\. Personal Information**  
Personal information is information that can be used to identify specific persons (for example, names, birth dates, personal ID card numbers, addresses, telephone numbers, E-mail addresses, occupations, education, work experience and related information). In general, you can visit us on the internet without telling us who you are or giving us personal information. However, in order to improve our service quality, it may be necessary to ask for personal information to fulfill your requests and provide better service. Neusoft is entitled to take measures to validate the authenticity of personal information you provide. If you give us personal information from somebody else, we will assume that you have their permission to do so. Neusoft is committed to not disclosing your personal information to any third party other than Neusoft and its affiliates unless it’s your own willl. 

**2\. Collection of Your Personal Information**  
We will ask you when we need your personal information to provide a service or carry out a transaction that you have requested, such as receiving information about Neusoft products and services, joining a limited-access premium site, signing up for an event or training, or when purchasing, downloading and/or registering Neusoft products, customer satisfaction surveys, market research and promotion, job employment, legal compulsory regulations and so on.

**3\. Use of Your Personal Information**  
Any personal information you provide is used and shared by, and among, Neusoft and its affiliates only. The use of your personal information is only for us to understand your requests and to provide better service and transaction. It may be convenient for us to provide you with service and contact you by using your personal information.

**4\. Security of Your Personal Information**  
We are committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. 

**5\. Protection of Minors’ Personal Information**  
Neusoft.com does not knowingly collect any personal information from minors. The personal information of any minor you provide shall be agreed by the minor’s guardian in advance. Minor is defined in accordance with the laws applicable to the Privacy Statement.

**6\. Use of Cookies**  
Neusoft may save some information as cookies into your computer when you are visiting the Site. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. The purpose of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. That we use such technology does not imply that we can automatically acquire any personal information about you. Neusoft.com may also use Web Beacon technology or other technology to regulate the site and to provide better service. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies.

**7\. Links to Other Sites**  
Neusoft.com may contain links to other web sites. We are not responsible for the Privacy Statement or the content of other web sites.

**8\. Legal Disclosure**  
You have acknowledged that the Site does not make responsibility for possible legal disclosure of your personal information without your consent in advance in accordance with the compulsory provisions of law.

**9\. Changes to This Privacy Statement**  
Neusoft reserves the right to modify and interpret this Privacy Statement. We may update and publicize this Privacy Statement from time to time. Any update shall come into effect from the date of publication. Please visit the Site regularly to keep appraised of updated content.

**10.** This Privacy Statement or any behavior relating to the use of this Site shall be governed by the laws of People's Republic of China. Any dispute arising therefrom shall be settled through friendly negotiations. Should no settlement be reached through negotiation, you agree that the case shall be submitted for arbitration to the People’s Court where the principal business address of Neusoft is located. 

**11\. Contact Information**  
If you have any question or suggestions, you may contact Neusoft. We will then do our utmost to resolve it.

Updated: Dec. 14, 2011
